spiritofchennai.com 2011-01-08

# Privacy Policy - Data security statement

Protecting the individual's privacy on the Internet is crucial to the future of Internet-based business and the move toward a true Internet environment. SpiritOfChennai.com has created this privacy statement in close resemblance to Fortune 500 companies that have shown and demonstrated their commitment to privacy protection on the web.

#### Consent

        By using this Web site, you consent to the collection and use of the information as described here. If we decide to make changes to this privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you will always know what information we collect, and how we use it.

#### Use and Purpose of Collected Personal Data

        On our Web sites, we only store personal information relating to you with your permission. You may choose to reveal information to us if, for example, you register or complete a survey. Companies in the SpiritOfChennai.com group may use the information internationally in connection with processing your inquiries and orders or to help improve our products and services.

        We would only share such information with third parties outside the SpiritOfChennai.com group with your express permission or as required by the applicable law. Information is used solely for the purposes described below.

#### Privacy Across the Entire SpiritOfChennai.com Network

        We operate many websites targeted at specific audiences across the globe. Any information that you submit to one of our sites in any one country may be sent electronically to a server for one of these sites in another country. We safeguard your privacy interests around the world by ensuring that this SpiritOfChennai.com site adheres to our international data-protection principles described in this statement.

We bind our employees to observe your privacy and confidentiality rights.

#### Online Security

        SpiritOfChennai.com supports secure online shopping using secure server technology because we want your shopping experience to be simple and safe. There are state-of-the art security arrangements and facilities on SpiritOfChennai.com sites to prevent security abuse. (Coming Soon Feature of SpiritOfChennai.com)

### Details

#### 1\. What Information Do We Collect and Why?

**IP Addresses**  
        We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems, to administer our Web site, and to gather demographic information. When you visit our site, we recognize only your domain name and not your e-mail address. We will see your e-mail address only if you give it to us by filling out a form or by sending us an e-mail message. We also record your browser details, which helps us create a ever user-friendly website.

**Cookies**  
        We use cookies to deliver personalized content, to save you having to re-enter your password repeatedly, to keep track of your shopping cart, and to tailor our information offerings to how you and others use the site. (Yet to be Instantiated)

**User Registration**  
If you choose to register, we can send you requested information or products, other product information, news, or promotions.

**E-mail Addresses  
        **If you choose to give us your e-mail address, we will communicate with you via e-mail. We do not share your e-mail address with others outside the SpiritOfChennai.com group of companies. You can choose not to receive any more e-mail at any time.

        Depending on how your e-mail application is set up, information about you may be transmitted automatically when you send e-mail to SpiritOfChennai.com.

        If you choose to register for third-party services, we may need to send some information from your SpiritOfChennai.com registration to the service provider, possibly including your e-mail address -- but only if your requested service cannot be provided otherwise.

**Shopping or Event Registration**  
        Our site includes order forms that you fill out to request information, products, and services. These forms collect your financial information, such as your banking details or credit card numbers. SpiritOfChennai.com promises to use any financial information that you submit solely for billing and payment purposes for that special transaction.

**Online Surveys**  
        Our surveys may ask you for demographic information, such as postal codes or your industry sector. If the online survey collects contact data, we may use that data to send you further information only if we specifically asked for your permission in the survey. You are free to retract any permission you gave.

#### 2\. Links to Other Sites

This site contains links to other sites. SpiritOfChennai.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites.

#### 3\. Choice/Opt-Out

You can opt out of receiving e-mail communications from us whenever you like. You only need to e-mail us to have your name and details removed from SpiritOfChennai.com's e-mail list or registration database. Registered users may opt out at any time by the same procedure.

#### 4\. Inquiries

        If you have any questions about this privacy statement -- if, for example, you wish to inspect or update the information we hold about you -- feel free to contact:

Administrator  
SpiritOfChennai.com  
Or e-mail: admin@SpiritOfChennai.com
